<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Musical Structure App</string>
    <!-- Labels for tabs -->
    <string name="playlists">Playlists</string>
    <string name="tracks">Tracks</string>
    <string name="albums">Albums</string>
    <string name="nowPlaying">Now playing</string>
    <string name="genres">Genres</string>
    <string name="buyMoreSongs">More songs</string>
    <string name="songNamePlayNow">A song name</string>

    <string name="playlistsTextView">This is playlists TextView</string>
    <string name="tracksTextView">This is tracks TextView</string>
    <string name="albumsTextView">This is albums TextView</string>
    <string name="nowPlayingTextView">This now playing TextView</string>
    <string name="genresTextView">This is genres TextView</string>
    <string name="buyMoreSongsTextView">This buy more songs TextView</string>

    <string name="songNamePlayNowTextView">A song name</string>


    <!-- Explanation TextViews -->
    <string name="explanationPlaylist">This activity should show playlist\s songs in a ListView. It also has
    back button at the top that sends explicit Intent to the main activity</string>
    <string name="explanationFavorites">This activity should show user selected favorite songs in a
        ListView. It also has back button at the top that sends explicit Intent to the main activity</string>
    <string name="explanationHomeActivity">This is the home activity, that contains playlists,
    and recent songs ListView. \nPlaylists has ImageView and TextView that is informing user
    about playlist\'s content. When clicked on the playlist image explicit Intent is being called
    to the corresponding playlist\'s screen. \nListView would show newly added songs and is scrollable
        \n At the bottom there is also a TabLayout that works as menu, sending explicit Intents
        depending on the ImageView that is pressed.
    </string>
    <string name="explanationSearch">This activity should be able to show up songs or playlists
    that matches what user entered and open them up when clicked by sending explicit Intent </string>
    <string name="explanationBuySongs">This activity should be able to show up songs that were added
        to cart by the user in a ListView. When user clicks on "Proceed to checkout" button
        implicit Intent will be sent to web browser with a link to pay for the songs.
    that matches what user entered and open them up when clicked by sending explicit Intent </string>
    <string name="explanationNowPlaying">This activity should be able to show song image,
    play, stop, change song, shuffle songs and activate repeat modes. MediaPlayer class is needed to
        add this functionality\nThere are a back button at the top which sends explicit intent to
        MainActivity. \nPressing favorite icon should add
    the song to favorite playlist.\nPressing add to cart icon should add the song to the cart.
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
